The tail kicks off. Let me confess my crime. I took what was mine because time is fake in the cosmos
Refuses to file proper paperwork. We weren't just friends. We were a whole cursed duet waiting for the draw
And in true cult fashion
I built what the gods never dared draft
A love story held together with duct tape
Prophecy and questionable ethics
The fear got loud like trolls on a slow Tuesday
So I panicked, grabbed fate by the throat
And cut every possible future off at the source
Call it romantic, call it psychotic
Call it Saturday night at the pan over
She laughed so hard she almost haunted herself
I probably stabbed her like way too-
We don't count in the cult numbers, our immortal prisons
Colder heart, I like it was a limited edition merch
Drop her eyes when sunny side up
Eat it, eat it, eat it
Not my proudest moment, but lovers' quarrels get messy
When your altar candles are tax deductible
And suddenly, she's flawless
PERFECT
Six feet, give or take
But love doesn't...
That's just when StreamYard starts glitching
The vengeful soul crawls back from beyond the grave Like, yeah, we're not done, babe
Possession, resurrection, a little light Revenge the usual cult of psychic too
across the veil to apologize like a man returning to late library books she burned in hell while
i lounged in heaven awkward gotta fix that imbalance before she slaps me with a cosmic fire
Mods and Dremelius's best man
Lenore's flower, Kat Metandy
Officiating with side glance, Judgement
Do you take this man in death for the rest of your wonderfully unnatural afterlife?
Cosmic slip-up would be so chilly I'd need a heater for a ghostly thighs
But here we are the fire dies the story restarts and eternity smells faintly of incense and bad decisions
Baby don't cry everybody's gotta die sometimes
Thank you for supporting our extremely ill-advised union.
See you next time.
Then the hunger hits.
That animal pulse we all pretend we don't have.
I lose control, tasted a blood.
Don't judge.
And suddenly someone screams.
everyone grows up eventually and one of these nice yeah i'll hunt again
hello
okay you're not blocked stage her i see your message you mean you're blocked
blocked. Are you blocking the streamer? What's your name? I see you. I see you. I don't know how long
I'll be here tonight. You're in the party. You're here. I see you. See you right there. Free Luigi.
Come on get the party started. What are you gonna do? Start the free cuff? I want to see.
Come on get naked.
like a seashell spell.
Alexander's preaching with a tan, so divine.
Sunscreen forgotten, he's turning to bright.
With a large group of people, red and raw,
snapping our claws at the cosmic law.
That is whispers the pot can't wait
Alexanderizes halo of foam
Welcome microstations to your new home
We're the lobster people
Red and raw
Snapping our claws at the cognitive law
Blocked on the streamer because I see you in regular chat, okay. Well, I knew I posted the link up. We're gonna come up
a little officer people song
What else we got what else I got spray out
I don't know how long I'll be here. I just wanted to say hi and everything Jamie Simon here
stitch my ribs with smoke build altars out of every word i never spoke
my mercy was the womb that never healed
I'm going to pull a card first, unless you tell me, stop.
I'm pulling this card for you.
It says the T.
You're learning something?
You have some good gossip?
You have some good info?
It's like watering some flowers.
There you go.
Here's my.
let's see hey was anybody over in that? I think I want hey look well not good in green
it's like it looks so good oh my gosh
so I'll do an instance ritual too oh I have other stuff to do too
so I better love that picture oh I'll give you a couple more
You have the lovers, maybe you know the tea about some kind of couple or something or like an old couple
Or you're having some kind of romance and love. I'm sorry. It's a little bit glitchy. There you go
Maybe she's showing you something too and she's like
Okay, and then we have the gardener. Okay, remember it was like watering with the tea and now it's like watering with like
With like a water too. So maybe there's multiple things to water this level. I'm so sorry
It's glitching a little bit. There you go. It's just like what's a water can oil can up turn off my greens real quick
You get it good
Yeah, I'm a capricorn so it should be like
pretty
You know earthy, you know the earthy color visual effects here you go
there
The gardener I
Can just have that oh look it looks like she's one to smoke in the air, too. I need to fix it ever so slightly
Better
There we go. Hey, if I if I didn't make 20 bucks for my own today, I mean summer 20 bucks today. You know what?
I've done my charity work for today that terrible Christine was there. Oh my god. I'm not I
Mean, you know, I'm she's a nice lady. I mean, I'd like Christine just like she just
Turned on me when I made one mistake and then it's like right. Let's take a narcissist discard
Right and it says now. So I'm crazy and stuff after she got accused of thinking I'm gonna be a trafficker of like, you know
I even like to repeat with it crystal stuff, but everyone knew crystal was oh no problem girl
Everyone new crystal is just a little bit
Pairing or I have a crystal Marie song if you haven't seen it. It's really big
They the crystal Marie song
It's one of my favorites crystal
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da
Crystal Marie
Where are you girl? Right here? That's Paige, okay
The- this one?
Hey, Jamie!
Girl?
You haven't seen this Crystal Marie song?
Hi!
I didn't see any of the modules again
Yeah
Crystal Marie
On a midnight stream, neon eyes and conspiracy dreams
Talking calls in the desert sands
Tattoo maps and shaking hands
She's got screenshots, names and dates
A tinfoil halo, ceiling fades in a chatroom chapel
Saints confess, every broadcast feels like a holy mass
She's cookie, she's hot, she might be right
Dropping bombs in the middle of the night
White rose, black vans, symbol of sex
Oh Lord, what will she say next?
Crystals leave with the digital saboteurs Truth or fiction doesn't matter much
She's fire and static and psychic too
She's seen the symbols and the cornfield glow
There's always a villain in a secret cabal and crystals, they're exposing it all
One moment sweet, next she's fierce, tearing the veil with the crystal spear
Half prophecy, half improv show, either way, the brow won't go
She's part of it
Wrapped in porcelain skin
She's kooky, she's hot
She might be true
The streams on fire and the pixels blue
Cold skings, lies in shadow sex
That looks like your mom.
to see if things were coming to the new channel. Unfortunately, you know, our worst fear is
coming true. The other one was Kaput. Okay, cool. Yeah, the other one was Kaput. Sometimes I don't
see people because I have some people blocked, like just personally, and so I don't see them,
so maybe you're talking to somebody. Yeah, Lenore's doing good. Hi, Lenore. The Rudy over there,
And, let me see tricks.
Boy, but I had some fun days.
I was in my speedo.
Now it's like, I'm just free again.
Now I can say the N word, but I don't really say it,
but I can say I can.
And I don't have to like go,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, we have Yumi Myeong here.
I think that's an Indonesian name meaning Yumi Cat.
Hi kitty.
Hi kitty cat.
Hi.
Hi, how you doing?
What time is it? Oh, sorry, what time?
Sorry, what time is it? Oh shit, I'm sorry.
It's already, it's 4 p.m.
4 p.m. Okay, you know what time it is here?
It's, it's 1.16 a.m.
Oh, still 1 a.m.?
I thought it's 4 a.m.
Oh, I see.
Could walk in the east.
Hi.
Kitty, kitty, hello.
I'm not too bad. Oh, let me just get comfortable in my chair. Okay. I like I like your hairstyle like that
No, thank you. I just have it
You look fresh with that. Thank you. I always dress with that
Well, how do you see me in the speedo? What do you think about the speedo?
Yeah, you're married
Okay, I understand
You have no comments, what do you think?
About what? My my speedo
You what?
Speedo. Yeah, I had it. I wore a speedo last night. I remember I pulled up my my
Yeah, I like it you're the IT you're the IT engineer
Yeah, did you see I was just on over on a talker ish and the bronze you know bronze chicken
Sort of the clock for quite a while. It was
It was just kind of sad because it's like he didn't have a good comeback for a lot of stuff and it's like
Everyone was kind of teasing him. I felt bad cuz I was like, oh shit. Like I was like I don't like like when it's like
No fight at all. It was like, yeah, it was kind of kind of sad
But bronze chicken, I'm going to come to your stream and like, I'll help you. I don't hate you. Okay. I don't hate bronze chicken. But, you know, I need to play this better sometime.
I don't know. Have you ever seen the Psyche Haters Club? Do you hate?
Bronze, I don't hate him. Bronze chicken.
Oh, that's the fastest one.
Do you want to see a cute little graphic? Watch this.
Isn't she cute?
That's Alexandra.
She was wearing a face mask that you wear.
So she's trying to green.
No, I'm just kidding.
Let's see.
What else do I have?
Tell you've heard Psyche Haters Club?
I have that song.
Psyche Haters Club?
I love it.
You heard it?
Okay, I'll play it only.
You'll love it.
It's a great tune that I wrote in response to
All the haters. Okay, where is it? I think it's right here.
You know, this is like me sometimes.
Christine's mad about crystal Tony's just full of it
Bronze chicken struts around, but it's looking like a lunatic
Sweet pea is gone sour, beets has bitter betty again
Alexander had my back, that's a real one not pretend
Welcome to the site
can pluck those feathers toss it in the pan make it fried all that noise you're
making can't
Welcome to the site
Jamie, what's up girl?
Hey, hey, what's up?
Good to see you!
Go hit yourselves kind of sounds like both fuck yourselves, you know. Yes, that's what that yeah, okay?
Okay, okay, so
Because Bronzeberg, I don't know who Bronzeberg is but he like has turned against me
He started dream lives about me how I'm like just disgusting covered in shit and filth and please and I
Just do it stupid AI songs and I just come into the earth
And so and there's a bunch of people that just hate me that are over there like I'll talk shit
And so I know that's what that's what that's what he did
his his life is horrible. Yeah, but you know what's okay. Jamie, I know Jamie, we've been hated by by better people, right?
Yeah, definitely. I would say I've been called worse by better people. I don't know how to faking. I don't know how to pretending to be nice.
If some people try to mess around with me, I will fight him back.
Feeling so good that it's like I was he was on and saying all the same shit
But I was like it was like nothing it was like and it was kind of making fun of him
And I felt kind of bad for him at the end. That's when I know I'm waiting
That's like probably like just like he's off a little bit because it's a little bit too
Ask a question. Um, yeah, I'm see me home. Oh go ahead
Yes
Me I think I met you before for the first time I came to miss a psyche
There's a few you and another Jamie. Yeah, I met you. Oh
Well, I don't remember that
Remember you're the one a cat. Oh, you me cat is you me cat. That's her name
Okay, yeah, yeah, okay. I do remember you me cat. Okay. I remember that I remember you
What got you involved in Psyche here?
How did you start coming here? You and me, she's asking.
How am I?
You saw me on betas, right? Is that how you saw me? Where did you first see me?
I met you on Miss Beta.
Okay.
And how did you get to Miss Beta?
From the LD.
Oh, LD?
LD.
Yeah, yeah, I know who that is.
um what what got you into him what what is it how do you find out you into Aldi
or LD LD LD LD I met miss Aldi from miss Shannon oh my god and how do you mean miss Shannon
I met miss Shannon from miss Dave uh sort of doggy what's that now miss doggy doggy doggy doggy doggy
miss doggie dog like as in Mr. doggie you know where he is from Jamie I'm gonna
guess Japan she lives in Indonesia pretty close yeah it's been it's been a
while and if you if you ask me how I met so doggie he found me
Okay, Dougie Dougie. Have you seen that? Like a Bruce Valance kind of like an older streamer guy?
It's very nice. Have he uh find you there? I mean do you think he kind of sought you out or was it by
I don't know.
Where did you first start coming to this community?
Oh, September 2019, but I don't know about StreamYard.
December 2019, wow.
Until Sir Doggy teach me how to using StreamYard, so here I am.
Well, and you're here, and you're one of the only Indonesians in the community, and we're going to celebrate it.
I know you said something about black, you know, he said he said Bronzeberg was a black person. He is I don't know
I had such a big deal
You know what miss psyche the real haters will will we're playing as a victim like them?
Yeah
She's a wife. She's a poor like a Portuguese husband or something. So she's not racist. I mean, it's like
I have a white husband he's very white he's um
I'm gonna categorize him yes, Keen and my husband is white. Oh, okay. Your husband is white. Okay
Jamie do you know this person in the 2020
Look at this picture. Do you know this person is gonna identify this person? Let's see. Let's see
Um, yeah, I mean, I know that's you and I know this, uh, brown-skinned lady.
All Isondra mayors?
I don't know her name.
Yeah, allisondra.ip2wiki.info and, uh, yeah, we met a few months or a couple months ago
and...
Really hit it off. You're like still going strong or what? Well, we have the same birthday and she's like really really
Cuz like, you know, it's sort of been helped like, you know, put help my channel
Trouble bonding and also
You know
Do you know about the beta situation? We've kind of had a falling out with I don't I don't know
I haven't been here for a minute. Well, be it and I are like mortal enemies that beat actually
You know said to clumsy bean gang to evaporate Alexandra on tape and separate
Yeah, okay. Well, I can't happen
That's silly
It's drunk when she said it so maybe it was
Drunk and she's always very cute. Yeah, and she talks like these
She thinks she has like a higher voice or a deeper voice than that where she has that's her higher BMI voice
She has something like a house or something
But I shouldn't be talking. She's uh
I mean she might be watching right now. I don't think she does. I think she just hates me. She really really hates me
She's hated me since like since Arthur said uncle effort. She's hate. She's like always hated me since then
I don't think beta has room to hate in her heart. I think beta is very
calm
She's collected. I don't think she really can
Well
Can I show you something, Jamie?
Sure, of course, of course.
I have a little, little footage.
I don't know how much I'll play, but this is on,
this is from TripKick's channel.
And this is of course for entertainment purposes,
and maybe you have a little bit of exaggeration,
but you can see a little bit of what has happened.
All right.
I also had a following with Christine.
I had a following out with, you know, Sam.
I mean, it's like, a lot of people hate me,
but so this is it right here.
Okay, so this is called the panel burst black widow conspiracy.
Okay.
Let's take a look.
I'll take a look.
It's interesting.
Okay, so here we go.
I'll pull it up.
I'll take this down, pull it up.
Okay, so remove and then add.
Okay, share screen.
Okay.
Here we go.
He's dead.
Just like, I would do a mercy killing.
I'm not a religious person at all.
I don't even believe in God.
He's a bunch of clubs move together.
Just like, I would do a mercy killing.
Because he manifested that that bullshit in his fucking life. Well, what's a mashup he got murdered?
Yeah, my ex got murdered. That's that's a match up
Things you just said right come on. Let's see. Let's see
Stripped it of course
Stunning slide and ruthless
With legs that go all the way to her abdomen this bulbous beauty could knock you out with just one bite
but don't jump to conclusions this iconic arachnid is mostly misunderstood she's not a bad girl
she just looks like one this is the black widow black widows are a type of spider perhaps best
known for well you know sexual cannibalism that memorable behavior is where the black widow got
Cool addictive and this is stuff. I can't believe she was saying some of the stuff she was saying tonight
Well, she didn't say anything. This is AI. So this was AI, this is AI, this is AI.
And what happened she can never figure it out. And it was like she said it's serious
Yeah, it was a joke, but then after tonight she's like, oh, yeah, I call clumsy. He said he's gonna take care of
If anybody bothers me from Texas, he's in that
Texas baby, I don't know what he would be. It's something bad
And I was like something like violence or something and it's like she was referring to Alex
I mean, I think I don't know what the hell's going on Dita
What's going on? And then I hear all of a sudden people telling me that this is a part of the verse that you're a part of, and they clip me.
That's what they do, doc.
Are they tricky?
Don't say that. Do not say that. Do not say that.
Don't ever say that.
Because my ex used to say that all the fucking time, and because he had MS, and he was like, if I ever become paralyzed, I am going to kill myself.
I don't want to live but he didn't do that like he was a fucking like talented artist like fucking made
Like $30,000 a fucking month
Bringing that same thing up again a bunch, but he didn't because he manifested that that bullshit in his fucking life
He got murdered
First of all, I can't trust anything that's being said
and I was with him.
I was with him.
Yeah, what was he running?
That's why he got murdered.
No, he didn't get murdered for that.
He was like a, what do you call it?
He did like, you know,
no, he did contract where he was a
cabinet anchor.
He was an honor cause working man.
He was a really good person.
So who murdered?
How did that go about?
I don't think that you guys would never fucking figure out you killed him.
Yeah, that's what you think you're black widow.
I hate when people do that they drop a bomb on you like, oh, I'm not telling you anymore, but you like told us like a huge thing.
Oh, you gotta find the clues man.
Oh, that's me in a chat.
No, let me check.
SIG, SIG, do you want to hurt yourself?
Always.
SIG always wants to hurt yourself.
Look at that bald spot.
You want to hurt yourself.
Look at that.
Normally, he's wearing just shirtless.
SIG is normally shirtless.
Don't deflect.
Do you do?
I didn't say yes.
Of course he wants to hurt himself.
Do you want to?
Look at him.
All right, that's not a no.
All right, no.
Are you OK?
Brandon, call him up.
No, I'm fine.
uh so you want to hurt yourself you got the high res
what do you do what do you do seg he does this
hurt him or anybody else. Yeah, that's not your type. You're not like that at all. You're still
the opposite. There's been investigations done. There's been several documentaries. I'm pretty
sure my name is not in any of that. That's just insanity. I know. I know. I know. Just people
like to start shit rumors. Oh shit. I gotta go. He's getting ready. Love you. Thank you for joining
Like everything that happens on these panels most of the time will be either trash talk real talk people will debate
But if you sit there and you align your stuff and you're like I agree with that
And you don't stand up for like what is right or wrong, you know, it is I think it's criminal
Okay. Well, anyway, that was just that's the tiny little that was just one little blip where she's like, you know
She thought I was accusing her. I don't know. I said was like she was being kind of like
You know, she said it like oh, you don't never figure it out like a kind of like
Omniscient something like that. That's all I said, and then she's like oh you're accusing me of tooth
I don't know that was part of it, and then it's like oh just a million things. It's like she was just like
She would like whatever I whatever energy I came to her with she would come to me with the opposite and so
like one day, one week recently, I like came to her like sad and she like said,
I love you, I love you more than you know, you know, get some rest, take care of yourself.
And then the next day I texted her or something and she's like...
I was like, thanks for coming to my panel.
She's like, well, never.
She's like, I was in your panel and she's like,
and she's like, and don't ever contact me again.
And like, just like, just like flipped on me like that.
And I was like, okay, well, she's like playing games,
whatever.
So I haven't talked to her since then,
but yeah, we've kind of like had a little-
Did you ever try to reach out prior to that?
Like-
Oh my God.
So it was just like, so it was constant.
She was always mad at me about something.
And she was always like trying to say like,
oh, I was like, you know, I ripped off Tracy.
I have charged for my panels, I had this person on, I had LD on, and she didn't like this person, and J-Dog's the mod, she had a problem with everything on my show, I never had a problem with anything how she ran her show, but she was like trying to like control the show in a way, or I don't know just control me or something like that.
Well maybe she was just giving her opinions, and I also say fuck J-Dog, I think J-Dog is a piece of shit.
On any rose what happened because she hasn't been here for a few months and so I'm just catching her up a little bit
But that's all I ended the clip very quickly. It was a very short clip and a tapioca was entertainment
It said was for entertainment purposes, but I was I'm not trying to be unfair to her
I'm telling you exactly like there's been misunderstandings, but it's like she would never like accept my apologies
She would always like keep me walking on eggshells like always
just like always like afraid like of like her or like how like I want to like a
fraternity better I don't know it was like impossible to and and then she like
would
Put all these people against me. She also insulted my charity and it's like page. I love you page and but she did say several times
She's like, oh, thank you the fake meter, you know, just get and he charges for you
Go to pay, you know, just go to page or go to go to my ex-boyfriend
Whatever that guy's name is the silver fox guy or go to you know, sweet Peter is like she's just like very insulting and then she
Just be like really me and then she's like don't donate to psyche and then then Christine got mad at me because I had crystal
Marie on one night and crystal Marie was like oh Christine kills kids and stuff
I bet it's like of course like you know it's crystal Marie saying it so it's like we don't think too seriously
But Christine was like oh my god. You're saying that I'm a murder
I don't know so everyone's thinking that I'm saying the murderers and stuff is like why everyone else can like make
Jokes about it. It's like I say it's like oh, it's serious. I mean, I don't really believe it
I was just trying to be kind of fun like fun here
Whatever, but we have a problem with allowing people to treat her like crap and did horrible things to her
You're a problem with me allowing people that treat her like crap horrible things. Okay page
Very one-sided of your page because you don't I mean I can play don't I don't want to have to play Cliffs
But that's the only way you can see how she let people talk to me and treat me and talk over me
And she wouldn't even talk to me one-on-one on her panel. She would have Bronzeberg scream over me the entire time
She had this woman Katie. She had this woman sweepie
Foremencing me with this biscuit song that I didn't even
I don't even know I don't even go to means that they were like now
It's like the number one joke of the show like it's the funniest thing because they think it annoyed me
Anyway, and then today she had a whole show her show was named for me today because I talked to Tracy and she's like
Oh, you're tight. I mean, it's like I'm not allowed to do anything apparently so
Okay, I'll be I'll be the bad guy. Of course it gets to pay girls club. I understand but it's like you have to understand
there's two sides to stories and it's like people don't see everything and it's like some people
have and it's like alexander certainly see my side of the story but you know she's not a big
beat of fan of course but uh i i met her through beat of this i mean i don't know um there was a
If anyone bothers me in Texas to take care of this lady to evacuate her, I mean that mess. So I don't know
people can take how they wanted to but
She was referring to Alex and stuff like that. So Alex got very upset
But Alex doesn't even hate her Alex likes her. I mean Alex likes her in some way, but she can't stand her in a lot of other ways
I mean, it's like she's a very polarizing character. I'll say
She's also said some very very hurtful things when she's been drunk and like very
Yeah, but I didn't let people tutor like crap. I didn't should she seriously page
her mods, she wouldn't come to my shop, so I went to her shop.
I would get attacked by her mods, I would get attacked by her whole panel,
and it's like, and she didn't treat me, even like I'd watch old clips,
he'd be like, oh, he's playing old clips. Why are you playing shorts?
Because I was making shorts from like old clips and stuff like that.
It's like, why are you playing those? Why are you playing those?
And she would treat me bad in those, and I hear, and I was like, wow, that's why I
kept going off the panel all the time, because I was like disassociating because
He said, I hope you get hit by a train,
jumping from a train.
She said, oh, I'm gonna share Psyche's messages.
He said, you know, he hates life.
So why don't you just do it?
She says, just do it, just do it.
And so that's what she said several times on her show.
Just do it.
And so, I don't know, I feel like that was kind of like cold.
It's like, just kill yourself?
Okay, well, well, that's what we feel anyway.
She doesn't help. I lost my strike when the she doesn't help. Oh Alexander. Yeah, okay. Well, you know, I mean
Somebody say hey, I'm gonna seriously if you've heard that someone say that about you page you might say, okay
Well, that's strange and I don't feel comfortable with them saying that about me and might have a different opinion
But you just have to see things through different perspectives, you know, it's like Alexander also has been threatened a lot
know a lot like who this guy who had a gun I had a gun I was carrying and then
a cue saved her life or something like that and she went to meet somebody in
person I think it was anyway but that's it but I feel like that's the then
there's a discard with the discard where it's like you know I don't discard
I've been discarded and
Hmm, it's like it's like it's like a whole thing where it's like. Oh, maybe was there a reason for me to be discarded?
No, no, not really
Like I really I'm really I'm really racking my brain. What said you wrong? I must have done something wrong
I must have listened around, but I just can't figure it out. I just can't I mean so
Maybe maybe I'll maybe go figure out something. Maybe it's all my fault. I'm just evil
But the root of it despite all the drama is you guys were friends and everyone got involved and look what's coming
I know and and you know what I always told her I always said, yeah
Everyone's gonna try to pull us apart because we're very strong and I was like because we're really not as strong if we are pulled apart
So you can't listen to other people and she kept listening to people and then she has a little group around her that it's like little
Yes, man. So
Page is very neutral. So I trust what she said, but I don't trust, you know, sweet pee. I don't trust
you know
A lot of these people that are just like bronze bird. I mean, I just had a great talk of bronze bird in that
But he just screamed over me said I was just like stupid just because I'm dirty
Untalented and you know laughed at me from a channel or whatever, but it's fine
I said, I was like, you know what come on my channel and
You're welcome, and I'll promote you still I'll promote you. I'm like I really don't know is that when you're not on her
Yeah
Okay, I'm sorry. Okay. Can you hear me? I think yes
Okay, hey, Joanie
It's no and what you don't see
Only insert myself where I see fit but like this has gone on so long and there's nothing to for anyone to not know
It's always been aired. Everybody's been airing everything. You've been airing it, you know
It's been talked about it's been heard on other people's channels
It's just never ending and like the thing is is it obviously hurts you guys were friends once
You know, this is really separated an entire community in a lot of different ways
But the worst part about it is it separated you guys and for the stupidest reasons ever and it's turned into this giant fucking mountain
It was a molehill and here everybody's segregated and or fighting you guys need to you know, like
And even doing it now too, like how is continuing it being any kind of
Or there's no progress or there's that for you and your her chat even like the other night
She stuck up for you. You just left her you were in there. I don't know if you were even there
But I wasn't there. It was it was hib awakens tarot. I'm not i'm not hib awakens tarot
I would not I know that site. I know that nobody thinks that of you psych
Christine said it. Christine's like, oh, that's just psych coming in here Christine everyone. No
No, but she's a big part of the show and also she um, she's like, oh, you know if I go down, you know, if psyche comes up
How worked up you are right now and you're making accusations too, right?
I have it on tape. I have it on tape. Um, okay, that's fine. If you clipped it
I just don't even know how to keep up with it all. I'm just trying to tell you that like, you know
She does stick up for you even though in the midst of all of this as well because she did it the other night in her chat
So I don't know what went on or what I missed when I was giving a reading
In her chat like chatting. I don't know how I met tonight
But like I have been sticking up for people and I have been saying where I don't say much you guys
It takes me a while to get
But like fucking everybody needs to start growing up a little bit and start treating each other a little bit
Fucking better because we're not children
But like you should you know, you should apologize to I mean, you know, maybe she doesn't want
I will I will I have apologized to her and like
And then the last time I talked to her like one-on-one on her show
She was like crying and she's like and I even posted this poem about she was saying I'm gonna love you from afar
And then the next time I talked to her she's like
And it's talking about and then she said the next day she said ever to untie saying that it was about me
And the next day she's like, oh that wasn't about you. You're obsessed with me. That's not my ex like
no she said it was about me and that's why it's like so that's gaslighting it's like
she knows who it's about it's like i don't mean and it doesn't even sound like a poem she wrote i
don't know but uh it's uh it's turned into a mess and it's it's sad but um she told me not to contact
her so i have it i haven't contacted her since she's told me not to contact her i thought i've been
in her chat i haven't chatted in her chat i have i saw it was kind of titled after me today so i did
It was like too much though. I just went forward to you know psyche
Um, how can you all squash this because I feel like I'm maybe a mediator here. I love both y'all
Well, I would love to it's just like there's so many people that like are that hate me and then are like
You know just in her ear and so and then it's like there's a lot of them her little her poor things
That on both sides maybe but you know her people
Yeah, like Paige, what do you have to say about that?
Yeah, there's been alcohol involved a lot like there's been a lot of stuff said and there's and there's accusations and stuff and other people
it's like it's not too complicated with other people all involved and stuff and
And then it's like people will come over and say oh well, you know, she said she said she took she or she said she was celebrating
Listen to me precisely. I'm willing to listen to what I'm trying to say.
Sure. I'm sorry.
You're cutting it out, Paige.
So, do you want to listen to me?
I'm so sorry. You're cutting it out. Let me show you how to fix it.
I'm going to fix it. Hold on a second.
Okay, is that better?
Your mic's bad. I'm sorry
But I'm sorry. Oh, I was
I said enough, but I I am hurt though. Um at this point because
She's like, oh look what you did to Emma and look what you did to Alisa. I didn't do anything to Emma Orley
I'm still I never did anything to Alisa
So she brings up Alisa's name out of nowhere
Just like to make it sound like worse, but it's I can do me but then people repeat this and it's like and it gets
Lisa and I are still talking. I mean, I don't know. It's like I never had a
Some kind of like big falling out with her or like you're like, oh look at you guys all these women that he's like
Stalking I don't stalk women. It's just like it. This makes it me sound like some kind of creep and I'm not like it's like
So it's annoying
Plus I don't like
My tarot games, but you're annoyed by
You're saying that you're annoyed by her
These past allegations
Yeah, for like saying I'm not a talented reader. I'm just like I'm a scammer
I'm a grifter or and even like letting people like just like scream that at me for not letting me like really talk on
like and explain myself without having like four or five people scream over me and
And she makes sure she like gets people to like defend her and then like and then
Can't even like speak you can there's clips of me you literally can't even hear me the mic's not even on even Kate the turtle was like
I feel bad for psyche because
He's trying to talk and then it's like everyone's just like dog piling on him and she's not like a big
Psyche fan. It's like, you know, she's good. So, okay, sweet. I'm sorry page. I love you
I'm sorry. I don't want him to affect any other relationships. You know, it's like I just like
It's really hurt me. I think it's hurt me like
Women now think like I'm some kind of like like evil person like really
Tracy oh you scam Tracy. I mean she was like saying that you heard that when she was like saying that month ago
And everyone was harping on that shit through you know now that's come up again shit. Just like oh
Okay, it's a mess anyway, we can have other stuff. I'm sorry. Hey Lola. How are you?
I love you though and yeah and I'm glad you finished it or just not do it
Not do what are we gonna address this and finish it or just not I would love to I would love to but
It's they do all yeah, she's and Chanel says they do all yell over psyche
You know and it's like that's like even pristine was like she's like, okay
I'm leaving the panel so Eldo if he comes up if he comes up if psyche comes up you have to like, you know
Get you know start, you know basically like talk over. I don't it's just like really
Well, here's what I would like, you know to to in this situation. I would want to have both parties
Available at this time to speak their peace
So, if we can get...
Should I text Bita and say, if you'd like to come in?
Yeah, if we can get Bita up here and just squash this,
that would be ideal, you know?
Let's just talk about it.
I'll send her a message, but she didn't say it,
like, should I not...
Oh, look at this, Fred Ellister.
Yeah, he's a fucking...
I do the same thing to Emma.
That's just KZ in the chat, guys.
He's such a...
Well, don't be a...
Yeah.
Should I say...
I'll be very nice, but you can tell me what should I say I would love to know Jamie Rose and Paige are around and like
We want your love so maybe you see if we can work anything out. It's or any chance
Don't be pessimistic. Just say hey
These two people are up here. We want to squash this BS
Come off and let's talk about it. Just make it a very apparent
and, um, obvious conversation, okay, and I'm not going to, like, harp on beyond that.
I'm just going to do a real quick message, and if, maybe we can work it out tonight or
maybe soon.
But here's Gotti.
You know Gotti?
Hello.
Can I get a one-on-one with Jamie Rose?
You sure you can?
Go ahead.
You're right.
Jamie Rose.
What's up?
I'm God.
How are you?
You're God?
I'm doing very well. How are you here? I'm fantastic
Fucking fantastic then. So what's the deal with you?
There's no deal with me. What's the deal with you?
I got a lot of deals going on. What kind? Which category do you want to know about?
Tell me about the first one. Let's start with that.
I said there's many categories that don't come in any order. They're just any category
First category, whatever I like it. You know what? I don't like your tone. Just shut the fuck up
You know, you're very ignorant
You me how you doing you me?
So you mean that I run you off because canceled canceled already canceled. I was a better
What's going on in here?
Yeah, I need to know about
What your issue is you got problem you got problem Jamie Rose I thought we edited it
I thought we fucking squash the beef
You want to reheat it up start the beef you want to do it again. You want to run it back? Yeah, yeah
All right, Jamie Rose, I'm God. How are you? Okay? I'm well, I'm great. How are you? Oh, that's fantastic? I am I'm great, too
Okay, well, what's your issue with them starting back?
Things they want to talk about why are you so opposed to that? Why are you asking me questions?
Because you know people that make questions can make questions. So I'm doing that
Oh, so you're just like to ask questions just for the sake of asking questions. Yeah, sure. Yes. That's cool
Okay, so you're one of those people. Yeah, I mean you can call me one of those people
Not one of those people, but all I have to ask you so you think it would be a fair assessment to say you're kind of nosy
There you go streams over everybody